buongiorno.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy & COOKIE Policy – Buongiorno

This policy describes the management of our web site as regard to processing activities concerning your personal data when visiting us at the following web page:

**www.buongiorno.com**

(the “ **Website** ”)

The present Privacy Policy is an information notice provided to any entity having to do with the web site http://www.buongiorno.com/ (hereinafter, the “Website”) of DOCOMO Digital Italy S.p.A., (previously Buongiorno S.p.A.), an Italian incorporated company with registered office in Milan, Italy, via Cosimo del Fante, no. 10, 20122, in its quality of Data Controller (hereinafter, the “Company” or the “Data Controller” or “Buongiorno”).

This information only applies to the above-mentioned Company’s Website and does not concern neither the web sites that may be visited by a user via external link, nor those services provided by the Company – in this regard, please refer to the specific privacy policies of such services, in order to know how the Company processes personal data of users who subscribe to its services.

Certain services or information offered on the portal may be subject to a different privacy policy. In such instances, a separate privacy policy will be posted.

“You” in this Privacy Statement means you as an individual.

“We” or “us” in this Privacy Statement means, in relation to your personal data, the Data Controller, namely DOCOMO Digital Ltd.

The Data Protection Officer (“ **DPO** ”) designated by the Data Controller, pursuant to Articles 37, 38 and 39, GDPR, is appointed and you may contact the DPO at the e-mail address dpo.dditaly@docomodigital.com or via post at the address in Milan, Italy, via Cosimo del Fante, no. 10, 20122.

#### 1\. **WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?**

“Personal data” means information about you.

When you visit this Website we may collect personal data either:

  * directly where you are asked to provide data. If you use any “connect” feature of the Website you may need to provide your name, contact information plus any other information needed as well as information about the page you are on or the content you are viewing; and/or
  * indirectly, such as using cookies (as described below) or to track your use of certain pages of the Website (e.g. your internet protocol address) and other technical means to monitor your use of the Website.

We do not seek to collect sensitive data through the Website.

#### 2\. **WHY WILL PERSONAL DATA BE USED?**

We may process and use personal data collected via this Website for the following purposes:

  * to administer the Website;
  * to provide information about products and services to you at your request – for example to tailor the content you see on the Website to your specific needs; and
  * to properly respond to your feedback and questions; and
  * for any other purposes required in order to allow us to provide our services.

#### 3\. **ARE COOKIES USED ON THE PORTAL?**

Cookies are information sent by a web server to a user’s computer, which are stored therein.

In order to know which cookies are used on this Website, please visit this page. If you want to refuse the use of any cookie, please correct the settings of your internet browser (in this regard, you can find details on how to undertake this action on the website of your browser) or change your settings on the following website http://www.youronlinechoices.com/.

In this case, please reminded that the web navigation and the enjoyment of the contents of this Website could be compromised.

#### 4\. **YOUR RIGHTS AS A DATA SUBJECT**

In relation to the processing of your personal data:

  * you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you;
  * you may request the update, correction and integration of the data, as well as to object, on legitimate grounds to the processing, entirely or partially, of your personal data, even if relevant for the purpose of the collection;
  * in certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records;
  * you have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organization (“data portability”);
  * in the event that we refuse your request under rights of access, we will provide you with a reason as to why.

In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being processed by the Data Controller, or how your complaint has been handled, you have the right to lodge a complaint directly with the data protection authority and the DPO.

For any further information about the processing activities carried out by the Data Controller, and/or the exercise of your rights, you may contact the Data Controller at the e-mail address press@buongiorno.com

As an alternative, you may contact the DPO at the e-mail address dpo.dditaly@docomodigital.com

#### 5\. **IS PERSONAL DATA TRANSFERRED TO ANOTHER COUNTRY AND IS PERSONAL DATA DISCLOSED TO OTHER ENTITIES?**

The website is located on a server in the European Economic Area.

Personal data collected from you is stored in data centres as well as cloud networks which are located or hosted in the European Economic Area.

When your personal data is transferred to parties located outside of the European Economic Area we shall take appropriate measures to ensure such third party will provide adequate security of such personal data and respect your rights to privacy.

We take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal data is treated securely.

#### 7\. **HOW LONG IS PERSONAL DATA RETAINED FOR?**

We will keep your personal data only as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. If you leave us your personal information will be delated from the website within a few weeks of your departure.

#### 8. **WHO IS THE DATA CONTROLLER AND DATA PROTECTION OFFICER?**

The Data Controller is DOCOMO Digital Italy S.p.A., (previously Buongiorno S.p.A.), an Italian incorporated company with registered office in Milan, Italy, via Cosimo del Fante, no. 10, 20122.

The Data Protection Officer (“ **DPO** ”) designated by the Data Controller, pursuant to Articles 37, 38 and 39, GDPR, is appointed and you may contact the DPO at the e-mail address dpo.dditaly@docomodigital.com or via post at the address in Milan, Italy, via Cosimo del Fante, no. 10, 20122.
